50 years have passed.
But I do not age.
Time has lost its effect on me.
Yet the suffering continues.
Aku's grasp chokes the past,
present, and future.
Hope is lost.
Got to get back --
back to the past.
Samurai Jack.
Father!
Shhhhhh!
But Aku -- he --
Quiet, lass!
We know!
The whole world knows.
Akuuu.
Grandpa! Grandpa!
Now, now, children,
settle down.
I know.
Get on with it,
ya blasted bag of bloated --
Dad, we can't hear.
He's on.
Ooh, sorry.
Long ago in a distant land,
I, Aku, the shapeshifting
master of darkness,
unleashed an unspeakable evil.
But a foolish samurai warrior
wielding a magic sword
stepped forth to oppose me.
Before the final blow
was struck,
I tore open a portal in time
and flung him into the future,
where my evil is law.
Now the fool seeks
to return to the past
and undo the future that is Aku.
Not!
Because, after all these years,
I have captured Samurai Jack
and the sword!
No!
Samurai.
Jack.
Oh, no.
Friend.
Oh, dear.
To all those fools
who dare oppose me,
your hero is dead!
Your hope is dead!
I am the one true master!
Let this be a lesson to all!
Time to die,
Samurai Jack!
Huh.
You know,
after all these years,
I'm not really sure
how I want to do it.
Ashi.
Fight, Ashi, fight.
I know
you're still in there.
Ashi.
Please, Ashi, fight.
Wait a second.
This is the one.
Or is it too much?
Perhaps a little less?
Madness!
Yeeeees.
Daughter, will you
do your father a favor
and kill the samurai?
No, Ashi, no.
Yes, the simplest solution
is usually the best one.
Ashi, you can't
let it end this way.
Please, Ashi, fight!
Fight!
Huh?
What the...?!
We're here, Jack!
We're here to rescue you!
Pathetic fools!
Urgh!
Ha!
Flying monkeys?
No, jump good.
Now, who's this?
The three hundred fight
for the one.
You're nothing but
insignificant insects to Aku.
And insects get squashed...
and exterminated!
Hold the line!
Aah!
Oh, dear!
Huh?
Aah!
No, wait!
Jackie boy!
Right.
Keep forgetting about that.
You -- You're dead?
Aye, just a wee bit.
Then how...?
Celtic magic!
Oi! Ya gotta meet
me bonnie daughters!
There's Flora, Maeve,
Isla, Bradana,
Murdina, Alana,
Oban, Ardbey,
Fionna, Assie,
Bonnie, Lorna,
Mawina, Shona, Nora, Piesil,
Shanath, Euspeth, Edme, Freya,
Gilbartha, Gesha, Grizela,
Innes, Dawntha, Cora,
Davina, Kina...
So many.
Aye, me pride and joy.
Now, take your pick.
I'd be mighty proud.
I cannot.
Wha?!
You're suddenly too good
for me girls?!
Oh, no, no.
I-I met someone.
Who?
Her.
I don't think she's your type,
laddie.
We've commandeered this samurai
to save you, Samurai.
A giant stone samurai?
Really?
Now, you don't see that
very often.
Jack?
Ashi!
Mawh!
Enooooooough!
Oh, dear.
Shields!
Dad!
No one harms
me bonnie girls!
Fear the call of
the phantom pipes of Lagavulin!
Ashi.
Ashi!
Jack?
Yes, I'm with you,
but you must fight, Ashi.
Fight it!
I...
I can't.
Ashi, you must!
Ashi!
I love you!
Is he dead?
No.
And he never will be.
How dare you talk back
to your father?
No.
You're not my father.
Yes, I am!
No, you're not!
Raaaah!
Aaaaaagh!
Huh?
Whaaaaa?
Ashi,
you have Aku's powers.
I do!
Oh, no.
Ugh.
You might have
beaten me now,
but I will destroy you
in the future.
There is no future
for you, Aku.
I disagree.
What trickery is this?
Aku!
Do not worry, Samurai.
You will see me again,
but next time,
you will not be so fortunate.
What?
Huh?!
You're back already!
Aaaagh!
No, wait!
Aah!
Aaaaaaaaaaaaagh!
No more!
It is done.
Ashi?!
I'm okay.
I felt him leave me.
He will never hurt anyone
ever again.
Ashi!
Jack.
What's wrong?
Without Aku...
I would have
never existed.
No.
Ashi.